(Penny(arriving with a man in tow):)I'm hoping.
(Sheldon:)Renaissance fair?
More of a medieval-slash-
Age of Enlightenment...
(Sheldon:)...slash-
any-excuse-to-wear-a-codpiece fair.
(Penny:)Okay, fine, whatever.
Um, you guys, this is my friend Eric.
- Hello.
ERIC: Hey.
(Leonard:)So, yeah, good to see you.
(Penny:)Yeah. Yeah, it's good to see you too.
- We should probably go.
- Yeah.
- Bye, guys.
- Like your hat.
(Howard:)Thanks, my mom made it.
Penny with a new guy. Très awkward.
(Leonard:)It wasn't awkward.
(Leonard:)It wasn't fun.
Besides, what's the big deal?
(Leonard:)We dated, we stopped dating,
and now we're both moving on.
By "moving on," you mean
she's going out with other men...
...and you spend the afternoon
making 15th-century soap with Wolowitz?
That was not 15th-century soap.
(Sheldon:)My god, those people need to learn
you can't just put "ye olde"...
...in front of anything you want
and expect to get away with it.
Can we please just go in?
My chain mail's stuck in my underwear.
(Sheldon:)You're wearing modern underwear?
(Leonard:)Relatively modern.
(Leonard:)What are you wearing?
(Sheldon:)I fashioned historically accurate
undergarments out of linen.
You went and bought linen?
(Sheldon:)Don't be silly.
I borrowed one of your pillowcases.
(Leonard:)Borrowed?